adrife.com 2012-09-06

# AdRife - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy was created in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. 

## Information Automatically Logged

This site uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site. This site records the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine the Internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages. This site uses page referrer data - that is, information about the page that linked you to this page - to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the Web. This data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources. 

## Personal Information

AdRife collects your name and email address, Internet Protocol (IP) address, and other pertinent information. This information is used to facilitate buying and selling of links/advertisements on the Internet. Unless requested by law enforcement personnel or required by legal process, we will not share any personal information with any third parties nor will we use any personal information for any purposes beyond those stated here. 

## Cookies

This site uses cookies for session management. See the Session Management section for more information about how cookies are used. 

## Session Management

This site uses form elements and/or cookies on each page to maintain a continuous user session. Form elements and/or cookies may contain a unique ID that identifies your browser session. Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Website. A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, and which your browser may then store on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Doing this will allow you to decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept cookies or not. Cookies on this site are used by ourselves, our ad management system, and occasionally by advertisers who use 3rd party ad serving solutions. Cookies are used for:

  * ad tracking,
  * customization of content (i.e. not repeating pop-up windows),
  * storing login information, and
  * statistical site-traffic analysis.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location. All credit card information is encrypted with 40-bit SSL encryption before it is transmitted across the network. AdRife complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information. 

## Contact Information

AdRife complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact [support@adrife.com](mailto:support@adrife.com).
